And for those who are already associated with us,
enrolled through us with ICC Lord, then
this workshop is going to be free for them,
absolutely free, but
you will have to enroll before the timely date, only then
you will get this free option. And for those who are
not associated through us
with ICC Lord,
what courses are
we going to teach for your life transformation in 6 days, which will be extremely powerful for you.
This entire process of ours,
such as what is cashless process,
what is reimbursement process,
how are these handled and
complete information about these will be explained to you in detail
[music]
[applause].
Hello friends, you are a
health insurance agent of ICC Lord and
you are not getting training. You feel
that if you get training, you can bring about a transformation in your life and can
build a huge health insurance business.
So friends, I am telling you good news and
tremendous news. Right now we are
launching a very amazing special workshop for the health insurance agency of ICC Lord, for which  The date is given here,
which you have to enroll as soon as possible.
This is going to be a very powerful workshop,
all the details of which I am going to
share with you in this video. Those who are
already associated with us,
enrolled through us with ICICI Lord, then
for those people this workshop is going to be free,
absolutely free, but
you will have to enroll before the timely date, only then
you will get this free option. And
for those who are not associated through us with ICICI Lord, the working will be on a chargeable basis,
whose cost will be only
₹5000000. There will be a
change.
We are going to teach you each and every thing in detail, in depth,
which will be extremely powerful for you.
Friends, my name is Yogendra Verma, I am a
health insurance expert. My work is to
train people, groom them, update them in the system.
And friends, if you want to become a hero from zero, then you must definitely
join this workshop.
Friends, let's quickly talk about
what all you are going to get scheduled here in six days,
that six days of powerful
working for you.  How can it be useful for you?
You just have to register for it and
update me. Those who are going to make the payment will have to make a
screenshot after making the payment and
those who are going to enroll will have to
share the screenshot after enrolling. Before proceeding further, you have to
subscribe to the channel, share it,
comment and definitely
click the bell icon, only then you will keep getting all the latest updates. Let us
quickly understand what
courses we are going to
teach here in 6 days for your life transformation, which will be extremely powerful for you.
Understand in detail. There is no need to delay,
you have to tie your seat belt
because the flight is about to take off here and I am going to
explain to you in detail
what all you will get to learn. Number one, the first
day will be very amazing for you, in which
we will teach you in detail about the entire terminology of health insurance.
Those who have come to the life insurance industry for the first time
or are absolutely freshers
or have come from the general insurance industry,
who do not know about the ABCD and B health insurance, then
friends, here
I am going to tell you all that. Here the
company profile of ICC Lord will guide you, you will be guided by the
payout structure.  We will tell
you how much commission you will earn here and how.
Thirdly, here we are going to tell you what
term logs are, what are they
called in basic terms, how are they
pronounced, what will be their purpose,
what will be their usage, you will
learn all this here on the first day. On the first day itself, you will be
taught about the prospecting list, which you will have to prepare.
How to make a listing of 50, 100, 200, 500 people,
each thing will be taught in detail,
what will be its purpose, that will also be taught to you on the first day.
This is the first day, let me tell you its timing
before moving ahead. It will
start from Monday. Your date in this will be Monday
from 11 am to 1 pm. The timing of the workshop
is fixed from 11 am
to 1:00 pm. It will be a 6-day workshop. If it is
starting on Monday, then the second day will be a holiday. The
third day will be the second day, that is,
these six days in alternate days will be
Monday, Wednesday, Friday. Next week, then
again Monday, Wednesday, Friday. Six days, complete
six classes.  Amazing classes are of two hours each
and in that we will teach you each and every thing in detail in
depth and those who will
enroll with us on a chargeable basis will
also get its recording so
I have already explained the first day, what is going to be taught to you on the second day, on the
second day we are going to teach you iPartner
portal in which you will
learn to take out quotations, you will
learn about other policies, you will be able to download their features, benefits,
brochures, everything from there, not only this,
you will also be
able to make a policy from there, we are going to tell you its entire journey as well, which will be
extremely powerful for you, it is
very useful, not only this,
on the second day we will do a role
play activity with you, whatever list you will make,
in that list we will do a
call with five hot prospects and will
show you by talking,
how to close your customer,
we will communicate that too in detail with you in a live meeting,
which will be
very powerful and very useful for you,
what is going to happen on the third day, the third day is going to be even
better, on the third day we will guide you
about a best plan, Elevate Plan
Which is very useful,
very amazing, this is an amazing plan in the industry,
you might have never seen such unmatched features, the
way of presenting it, the way of representing it
and what all
details will sell that plan, we will
guide you in this plan and will
talk about its case studies, will
also give you some reviews about other companies
which is going to be very powerful for you,
fourth day, on the fourth day
we will teach you in detail what is
our entire process like what is
cashless process, what is
reimbursement process,
how are these handled and complete information about these will be
explained to you in detail, fifth day, on the fifth day
you will be told how to do policies in EMI,
how to do policies in EMI through credit card
and which are your restricted hospitals, what are
blacklisted hospitals,
which are the special hospitals in our network where our
claim settlement is hassle free and easy and
a special feature from the company  It has come from
what is called Anywhere Cashless,
what is its purpose, all the detailing and
what are the new initiatives of ICC Lord,
about which you will be given information which will be
extremely powerful, this fifth day is going to be
with you and the sixth day which you will
never forget, in the sixth day we will
discuss with you about special plans, apart from the main plan, what are the other plans,
what are their
USPs and how the policy is properly
made,
complete information will be given about the fresh policy and port policy
so that you will
understand the complete journey from zero to the end, those who will
activate their code within a day and
login 000 policy, we will
provide them a trophy along with a certificate,
those who complete the 6 day training will get a certificate, that is for
Shore Health Expert, those who
login for a policy of 25000 will
get a trophy, those who login 50 businesses
within 6 days will
get the Super Champion trophy and  Those who will
login a business of 1 lakh will be
awarded with the Master Trophy and will be informed and
not only this friends, there are
some special basic
terms and conditions for joining this six day workshop, while joining you have to keep
your video on
from 11:00 am to 1:00 pm and we have to be
with us in two way communication,
whatever will be asked of you during the meeting you will have to
tell that is for sure
mandatory and not only this,
in the middle of those training we will give you some live question answers,
quiz which you have to do
live here and plus you will also
get an assignment for home, practicing which will take
your knowledge to the next level friends,
all this training is available for only 55000,
its date is given here,
you have to enroll, do not delay
and if you enroll before this date then the
agents who are associated with us will be
considered with us on a free basis
and those who are not associated with us
₹5000000
Already more than 500 agents from India have
become experts, have learnt in good working
and are
doing a great and wonderful business, you
can also be one of them, there is no need to delay, I
hope you have understood this content,
Hello, your friend Yogendra
Verma, thank you so much